Finding Aid for the S.A. Griffin collection of underground poetry, Scott Wannberg, and The Carma Bums LSC.2248
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Writings by Griffin, circa 1980-2015 (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 331, Box 332, Box 333)
  - Serials (Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 333)
    - Maintenant, no. 3. New York., 2009 Spring (Box 333, Folder 2)
      "Night of Mayhem" and "Beautiful Blessings" appear on page 33.
    - Maintenant, no. 6. New York., 2012 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      "I Saw Jesus Hanging With Mohammed" appears on page 63.
    - Maintenant, no. 9. New York., 2015 (Box 333, Folder 2)
      "The Digital Kind" appears on page 81.
    - Maintenant, no. 10. New York., 2016 (Box 333, Folder 3)
      "Presidential Candidate Upside Down Cake" appears on page 122.
    - The Mas Tequila Review, no. 7. Albuquerque., 2013 Summer (Box 22, Folder 5)
      "Sketch Of Two Older Women As Naked Lunch & One Young Man Surfing The Silver Shadow Of The Sunset Strip" appears on page 16.
    - The Lowdown. Ellison Bay., 2013 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
      Griffin's collages and poetry are published throughout this literary arts journal edited by Robert M. Zoschke (RMZ). RMZ's inscription to Griffin reads, "Hey S.A.--Your work makes the book work..."
    - Moon & Sun Review, no. 1. Venice., 2014 Spring (Box 22, Folder 8)
      "You Hate" appears in this issue.
    - Edgar Allan Poet, no. 3. Sherman Oaks., 2015 (Box 333, Folder 4)
      "Los Angeles in the Rain" appears on page 43, "Kitten with a Whip" appears on page 166, and "Ubiquitous Freud" appears on page 176.
    - MILK, no. 3/4. Los Angeles., 2015 (Box 333, Folder 5)
      "Kitten with A Whip" appears in this issue.
    - AMASS, issue 59, no. 3, v. 20. Los Angeles., 2016 (Box 333, Folder 6)
      "The Invisible Hand Discusses the Future of the World" appears on page 35.
- Writings collected by Griffin (Box 23, Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Box 55, Box 56, Box 57, Box 58, Box 59, Box 60, Box 61, Box 62, Box 63, Box 64, Box 65, Box 66, Box 67, Box 68, Box 69, Box 70, Box 71, Box 72, Box 73, Box 74, Box 75, Box 76, Box 77, Box 78, Box 79, Box 80, Box 81, Box 82, Box 83, Box 84, Box 85, Box 86, Box 87, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 91, Box 92, Box 93, Box 94, Box 95, Box 96, Box 97, Box 98, Box 99, Box 100, Box 101, Box 102, Box 103, Box 104, Box 105, Box 106, Box 107, Box 108, Box 109, Box 110, Box 111, Box 112, Box 113, Box 114, Box 115, Box 116, Box 117, Box 118, Box 119, Box 120, Box 121, Box 122, Box 123, Box 124, Box 125, Box 126, Box 127, Box 128, Box 129, Box 130, Box 131, Box 132, Box 133, Box 134, Box 135, Box 136, Box 137, Box 138, Box 139, Box 140, Box 141, Box 142, Box 143, Box 144, Box 145, Box 146, Box 147, Box 148, Box 149, Box 150, Box 151, Box 152, Box 153, Box 154, Box 155, Box 156, Box 157, Box 158, Box 159, Box 160, Box 161, Box 162, Box 163, Box 164, Box 165, Box 166, Box 167, Box 168, Box 334, Box 335, Box 336, Box 337, Box 338, Box 339, Box 340, Box 341, Box 342, Box 343, Box 344, Box 345)
  Writings collected by Griffin include monographs, largely related to the Venice West and Denver Beat poetry scene, other Beat poetry, and underground poetry from the greater Los Angeles area; serials, which include poetry and punk related zines and magazines; manuscripts sent to Griffin for publication, as well as proofs and galleys; clippings and publications referencing Griffin or his performance groups; and subject files of people and places in the poetry and punk communities.
  - Monographs (Box 23, Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Box 55, Box 56, Box 57, Box 58, Box 59, Box 60, Box 61, Box 62, Box 63, Box 64, Box 65, Box 66, Box 67, Box 68, Box 69, Box 70, Box 71, Box 72, Box 73, Box 74, Box 75, Box 76, Box 77, Box 78, Box 79, Box 80, Box 81, Box 82, Box 83, Box 84, Box 85, Box 86, Box 87, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 91, Box 92, Box 93, Box 94, Box 95, Box 96, Box 97, Box 98, Box 99, Box 100, Box 101, Box 102, Box 103, Box 104, Box 105, Box 106, Box 107, Box 108, Box 109, Box 110, Box 111, Box 112, Box 113, Box 114, Box 115, Box 334, Box 335, Box 336, Box 337, Box 338, Box 339, Box 340, Box 341, Box 342)
    The monographs, which are organized alphabetically by last name, largely relate to the Venice West and Denver Beat poetry scene, other Beat poetry, and underground poetry from the greater Los Angeles area which include Charles Bukowski's own collection of foreign editions of his work, which Linda Bukowski gave to Griffin. Many of the monographs are small press or independently published chapbooks.
  - Serials (Box 343, Box 344, Box 345, Box 116, Box 117, Box 118, Box 119, Box 120, Box 121, Box 122, Box 123, Box 124, Box 125, Box 126, Box 127, Box 128, Box 129, Box 130, Box 131, Box 132, Box 133, Box 134, Box 135, Box 136, Box 137, Box 138, Box 139, Box 140, Box 141, Box 142, Box 143, Box 144, Box 145, Box 146, Box 147, Box 148, Box 149, Box 150, Box 151, Box 152, Box 153)
    SUBSERIES CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
    The serials, which are alphabetized by title, are comprised of poetry and punk related journals, zines and magazines, including Bachy, Obras, Puppet Terror, Rats With Keys, The Rise and Fall of the Harbor Area, Spiegelman's Mailart Rag, and Sunset Palms Hotel.
    - 51%, v. 2, no. 1. Costa Mesa., 1996 September (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - 2B, no. 14. Chicago., 1999 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Abraxas, no. 44/45. Madison., 2006 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Accent. Urbana., 1957 Spring (Box 116, Folder 4)
      This issue is signed by Diane di Prima on page 111 where her "Poem" appears.
    - Adam Bedside Reader, v. 1, no. 47. Los Angeles., 1971 October (Box 116, Folder 5)
      This issue includes a Special Charles Bukowski Samplers and the cover model's chest is signed by Hank.
    - The Adventures of Principal X., undated (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Alcatraz, no. 2. Santa Cruz., 1982 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Aldebaran Review, no. 4. Berkeley., 1969 May (Box 116, Folder 8)
      This issue includes work by Douglas Blazek, Lyn Lifshin, Emilie Glen, and Alta. It was printed at Noh Directions Press by John Oliver Simon and Richard Krech. According to the title page, "Contents are not copyright since that would imply a willingness to employ pig penal system, but they are guarded and will not be misused."
    - Alpha Beat Press. New Hope., undated (Box 116, Folder 9)
      This Post Beat Independent Broadside is published monthly by Ana and Dave Christy and features Mark Hartenbach's "Chili, Cornbread, and The Blues."
    - American Film, v. 13, no. 2. New York., 1987 November (Box 116, Folder 10)
      This issue features Mickey Rourke, Charles Bukowski and the making of Barfly.
    - American Splendor Special: A Step Out of the Nest, no. 1. Milwaukie., 1994 August (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - American Splendor: Music Comics. Milwaukie., 1997 November (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - American Splendor: Odds & Ends. Milwaukie., 1997 December (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - The Amphibian, v. 1, no. 1. Reseda., 1990 October/November (Box 116, Folder 12)
      This issue includes work by Lisa Neal, Marcia Arrieta, Kris McHaddad, and Lyn Lifshin.
    - Angerbox, no. 3. Los Angeles., 1999 April (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Angry Thoreauan, no. 11. Anaheim., 1994 November (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Angry Thoreauan, no. 12. Anaheim., 1995 February (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Angry Thoreauan, no. 15. Anaheim., 1995 November (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Angry Thoreauan, no. 16. Anaheim., 1996 March (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Angry Thoreauan, no. 17. Anaheim., 1996 July (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Angry Thoreauan, no. 18. Anaheim., 1996 December (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Angry Thoreauan, no. 21. Hollywood., 1998 May-June (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Angry Thoreauan, no. 22. Hollywood., 1998 September-November (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Angry Thoreauan, no. 24. Hollywood., 1999 April (Box 117, Folder 1)
      This issue features Rev. Randall Tin-ear's "My Laugh At The LAPD" and "Fuck Work!" his interview with Unamerican Activities co-founder James.
    - Angry Thoreauan, no. 25. Hollywood., 1999 August-September (Box 117, Folder 2)
      This issue's theme is Coprology and includes a "Talkin' Shit with the Muffs" interview.
    - Angry Thoreauan, no. 27. Los Angeles., 2000 November (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - ANTE, v. 4, no. 2-3. Los Angeles., 1968 (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - A*PALzine, v. 1, no. 6. San Gabriel., 1993 July (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - APO-33: A Metabolic Regulator, no. 1. San Francisco., 1966 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      This bulletin distributed by City Lights is "A Report on the Synthesis of the Apomorphine Formula" by William S. Burroughs.
    - Arcade: The Comics Revue, v. 1, no. 3. Berkeley., 1975 Fall (Box 117, Folder 5)
      This issue is signed on the cover by Charles Bukowski and features his "Bop Against The Curtain" on page 29 with illustrations by R. Crumb.
    - Arcanum, no. 3. Denver., 1989 March (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Arshile, no. 11. Los Angeles., 1999 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Art & Scope. Oneonta., 1998 Fall (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Art & Scope. Oneonta., 1999 Spring (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Art & Scope. Oneonta., 1999 Fall (Box 117, Folder 8)
      This Millennium Edition is signed by Editor-In-Chief David Greenspan.
    - Art Fax, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1985 November (Box 117, Folder 9)
      This punk rock zine was created by Mike M. Mollett.
    - Art Gallery of South Australia. Adelaide., 1991 (Box 117, Folder 10)
      This catalogue for the Milton Moon Retrospective was written by Christopher Menz, Associate Curator of Australian and European Decorative Arts.
    - Arthur, v. 1, no. 13. Gaithersburg., 2004 November (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Arthur, v. 1, no. 24. Gaithersburg., 2006 September (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Artillery, v. 3, no. 5. Los Angeles., 2009 May/June (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Artillery, v. 6, no. 6. Los Angeles., 2012 Summer (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Art:Mag, no. 23. Las Vegas., 2000 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Art-Rite, no. 18. New York., 1978 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Ashes. Denver., 1981 September (Box 117, Folder 14)
      This Howling Dog Press monthly features Yr Daily Ace by John Loquidis with drawings by Steve Wilson. The dedication reads: To all the hookers of Denver without whom there wld have been no one to talk to -- & ain't that bad or good.
    - Athena Louise Replies., circa 1990s (Box 117, Folder 15)
      This zine prints problems and replies from Athena Louise such as Problem: Allow alcohol at least in the backyard! Reply: This is a problem you should discuss with the management. Jabberjaw, Los Angeles.
    - Aversion, no. 6. Chatsworth., 1986 Fall/Winter (Box 117, Folder 16)
      This issue features a review of Henry Rollins at Bebop Records and Scott Wannberg's "They Got."
    - AziMuth, no. 2. New Haven., 2001 Fall (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Bachy, no. 8. West Los Angeles., 1976 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      This poetry journal was published and edited by Papa Bach aka John Harris, along with a changing cast of others including Leland Hickman.
      This semiannual journal is "dedicated to the discovery of previously unpublished artists of worth." Publisher John Harris states, "We publish all kinds of material -- except sentimental, academic, or metaphysical bullshit."
    - Bachy, no. 9. West Los Angeles., 1977 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Bachy, no. 10. Los Angeles., 1977 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      This issue's silver cover features a photo of a woman in shades standing inside a Los Angeles party house.
    - Bachy, no. 11. West Los Angeles., 1978 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      This issue features multiple works by Wanda Coleman, including "Male Order Catalog" in which she references Sir Lady Java circa 1969 as the world's most famous female impersonator.
    - Bachy, no. 12. West Los Angeles., 1978 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      This issue features an interview with Holly Prado and the article, "Poetry in Los Angeles Since 1945: Part One" by Alvaro Cardona-Hine.
    - Bachy, no. 14. West Los Angeles., 1979 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      This issue contains William Mohr's review of Bob Flanagan's The Kid Is The Man and a collection of Wanda Coleman's poems including "Flight Of The California Condor/Wind Sistuh Blooded Eyes/Mind Full Of Flesh" for "Los Angeles -- you at my jugular."
    - Bachy, no. 16. West Los Angeles., 1979 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      This issue features "Feel The Leather," an interview with Wanda Coleman and collections of poetry by Coleman, John Thomas, and Kate Braverman.
    - Bachy, no. 17. West Los Angeles., 1980 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      This issue features an interview with John Rechy, "The Relentless Pursuit of Integrity" and three selections from Pablo!, his unpublished novel completed when the author was eighteen.
    - Bachy, no. 18. Los Angeles., 1981 (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - Back Off, v. 1, no. 3. Gardena., 1991 May (Box 118, Folder 5)
      An advertisement for Mondo Video when it was located at 639 Channel Street in San Pedro appears in this issue.
    - Bagazine, no. 2. San Francisco., 2007 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      Contributors to this "Assemblage - Bagism - Happening" include Charles Bukowski, Bill Roberts, Billy Childish, and F.N. Wright.
    - Bagazine, no. 4. San Francisco., 2010 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      Contributors to this "Assemblage - Bagism - Happening" include Billy Childish, Johnny Brewton, and Richard Krech.
    - Bagozine, Cleveland (Box 119, Folder 1)
      No. 29 (2004 October), no. 39 (2005 August), no. 40 (2005 September).
    - Bart Simpson's Creepy Crawly Tales, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1999 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Basura, no. 1. Laguna Beach., 1992 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Basura, no. 3. Laguna Beach., 1993 July (Box 119, Folder 3)
      A letter from zine creator, Bob Basura to S.A. Griffin may be found inserted between page 32 and 33.
    - Basura, no. 4. Laguna Beach., 1993 November (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Basura, no. 5. Laguna Beach., 1994 May (Box 119, Folder 3)
      This issue includes a letter to Bob, the zine's creator, from Jen Hofer.
    - Bathtub Gin, no. 17. Erie., 2005 Fall/Winter (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Beachhead, no. 217. Venice., 1988 February (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Beachhead, no. 269. Venice., 2003 November (Box 119, Folder 5)
      This issue includes "Elegy for Tony Scibella" by Bill Fleeman. Scibella died of a heart attack on October 28.
    - Beachhead, no. 270. Venice., 2003 December (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Beachhead, no. 272. Venice., 2004 February (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Beachhead, no. 293. Venice., 2006 February (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Beachhead, no. 310. Venice., 2007 August (Box 119, Folder 5)
      This issue contains an 8 1/2" x 11" black and white photocopy of a photo of Philomene Long and John Thomas alongside the following text: "We open a door/To where/There is no road/We take it."
    - Beachhead, no. 350. Venice., 2010 December (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Beachhead, no. 371. Venice., 2012 September (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Beacon Review, v. 3, no. 1. Seattle., 1984 Summer (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - The Beat Journals, v. 2. Coventry., 1995 September (Box 119, Folder 7)
      This volume contains "Jaggernaut," a short story by Charles Bukowski.
    - Beat Scene, no. 2. Coventry., 1988 Mid Summer (Box 119, Folder 8)
      This issue features the Neal Cassady jail letters.
    - Beat Scene, no. 3. Coventry., 1988 Autumn (Box 119, Folder 8)
      This issue features Rhoda Ryder's story.
    - Beat Scene, no. 4. Coventry., 1988 Winter (Box 119, Folder 8)
      This issue features Jim Burns on Lester "Prez" Young.
    - Beat Scene, no. 7. Coventry., 1989 Summer/Autumn (Box 119, Folder 8)
      This issue features a rare Jack Kerouac interview.
    - Beat Scene, no. 8. Coventry., 1989 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      This issue features an interview with Carolyn Cassady.
    - Beat Scene, no. 9. Coventry., 1989 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      This issue features Charles Bukowski holding a cat on the cover and includes interviews with William Burroughs, Lydia Lunch, and Jack Micheline.
    - Beat Scene, no. 15. Coventry., 1992 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      This issue includes Charles Bukowski's "Husk," Beat Scene flyer No. 1, given away to subscribers with this issue.
    - Beat Scene, no. 16. Coventry., 1993 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      This issue contains an interview with Ann Charters and a feature on Beat Women.
    - Beat Scene, no. 17. Coventry., 1993 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      This issue contains an interview with Professor Eric Mottram and a feature on The Fugs.
    - Beat Scene, no. 18. Coventry., 1994 January/February (Box 119, Folder 9)
      This issue contains an interview with Carolyn Cassady and a feature on Mal Dean.
    - Beat Scene, no. 20. Coventry., 1994 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      This issue is dedicated to Charles Bukowski and contains a pink chapbook inserted between the cover and the table of contents. This chap is number 11 of 75 and is signed by Bukowski. The cover art is a headstone with 1992 on it. The text is excerpted from a letter Bukowski wrote to Ann Menebroker on November 23, 1966
    - Beat Scene, no. 43. Coventry., 2003 Summer (Box 119, Folder 9)
      This issue contains a feature on Bukowski and The FBI and a profile piece on Kulchur, a 1960s Beat magazine.
    - Beat Scene, no. 48. Coventry., 2005 Summer (Box 119, Folder 10)
      This issue contains a feature on the Six Gallery and a piece on the Naropa University archives alongside a photo of William Burroughs and Anne Waldman at the Naropa University at Boulder, Colorado in 1975.
    - Beatitude, no. 17. San Francisco., 1960 October-November (Box 120, Folder 1)
      This issue was published by City Light Books and according to the editors, "MANUSCREEDS WILL NOT BE RETURNED even if accompanied by the usual return-postage scene. (The stamps will be unlicked and used for evil purposes.) The following are a few of the contributors: Allen Ginsberg, Jack Kerouac, Gregory Corso, Lenore Kandel, Lawrence Ferlinghetti, and Leroi Jones.
    - Ben Is Dead, no. 5. Hollywood., 1989 Summer (Box 120, Folder 2)
      Ben is God: The L.A. Newsletter #B is inserted into this issue.
    - Ben Is Dead, no. 11. Hollywood., 1990-1991 Winter (Box 120, Folder 2)
      This Obsession and Bad Habits theme issue includes an interview with Glen Meadmore of Pedro, Muriel and Esther, a drag queen speed metal parody band.
    - Ben Is Dead, no. 12. Hollywood., 1991 April (Box 120, Folder 2)
      This Censorship theme issue includes an interview KXLU General Manager Colin Sicc and an interview with Stuart Sweezey and Brian King of Amok Books.
    - Ben Is Dead, no. 13. Hollywood., 1991 May (Box 120, Folder 2)
      This Broke theme issue features The Ben Encyclopedia of Broke: An A-Z guide of tips, scams, techniques, and the like for getting by with a less-than-impressive cash flow.
    - Ben Is Dead, no. 16-17. Hollywood., 1991-1992 December-January (Box 120, Folder 2)
      This Gross theme issue contains a performance artists piece which features Bob Flanagan, Kembra Pfahler, Curtis York, Annie Sprinkle, Johanna Went, Lisa Suckdog, Deen Swaydon, Frank Moore, and Karen Finley.
    - Ben Is Dead, no. 18. Hollywood., 1992 March-April (Box 120, Folder 3)
      This Glamour themed issue features cover Supermodel Sean deLear, lead singer of Glue. An interview with the band appears on page 24.
    - Ben Is Dead, no. 19. Hollywood., 1992 June-July (Box 120, Folder 3)
      This "themeless" issue contains various features on the riots or uprising following the Rodney King verdict. The cover photo is of a sidewalk with "Bad Cop No Donut" graffiti.
    - bender, v. 1, no. 1. South Pasadena., 1997 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Best Buy Comics. San Francisco., 1979 February (Box 120, Folder 5)
      These stories and comic strips are by R. Crumb.
    - Best Poems of 1962, v. 15. Palo Alto., 1963 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Beyond Baroque, no. 7. Venice., 1996 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      This issue is dedicated to the memory of Bob Flanagan and William Bitting.
      Bob Flanagan was a poet, performance artist and Modern Primitive pioneer who influenced Griffin as a poet and performance artist. Flanagan was a long time facilitator for Beyond Baroque's Wednesday night writing workshop. When Flanagan passed away, Griffin went to the open poetry reading at Beyond Baroque where he was spanked while he read as tribute to Flanagan's poetry and performance.
    - Beyond Baroque, v. 26, no. 2. Venice., 2004 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      This issue is dedicated to Hubert Selby, Jr. in Memorium, April 26, 2004.
    - Beyond Baroque, v. 28, no. 2. Venice., 2006 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      This "Truth, Etc." issue is dedicated to Gary Webb, Hunter S. Thompson, and H.R. Shapiro.
    - Beyond Baroque 802, v. 11, no. 2. Venice., 1980 Spring (Box 120, Folder 8)
      This gay and lesbian theme issue is dedicated with love to David Goodstein, creator of "The Advocate Experience."
    - Beyond Baroque NeWLetterS, v. 5, no. 5. Venice., 1974 September (Box 120, Folder 9)
      The cover features Stuart Z. Perkoff (1930-1974) at Papa Bach's in addition to poems by Blakeslee Stevens and Neeli Cherry (aka Neeli Cherkovski).
    - Beyond The Blackout, no. 1. Hollywood., 1984 June (Box 120, Folder 10)
      This issue features interviews with The Cramps and John Waters.
    - Big Cigars, no. 3. Washington D.C., 1988 Winter (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - The Big Issue, no. 8. Venice., 1998 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Big Two-Hearted, v. 3, no. 1. Iron Mountain., 1988 Winter/Spring (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Bizarre Sex, no. 10. Princeton., 1982 (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Black Ace Books Catalog, no. 1. Aurora., 1971 February (Box 120, Folder 15)
      This "Modern Literature" catalog features a cover design by the Secret 6 and contains two poems by Larry Eigner.
    - Black Ace Books Catalog. Los Angeles., 1992 Spring (Box 120, Folder 15)
      This "Beat & Other Lit" catalog includes a letter from Rose Idlet and Tony Scibella printed on the inside of the cover.
    - Black Ace Books Catalog, no. 11. Los Angeles., 1993-1994 Winter (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Black Ace Books Catalog, no. 13. Los Angeles., 1996 (Box 120, Folder 15)
      This "Beat & Other Lit" catalog includes a letter from Rose Idlet printed on the inside of the cover. Gabrielle Idlet is the guest cover artist for this issue.
    - Black Ace Books Catalog, no. 14. Los Angeles., circa 1998-1999 (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Black Ace Books Catalog, no. 15. Los Angeles., circa 2003 (Box 120, Folder 15)
      The introduction to this "Beat & Other Lit" catalog was written by Tony Scibella. According to a note inside the cover, Scibella had just finished the catalog, fell ill for a few weeks, and died on October 28, 2003.
    - Black Cross Magazine, no. 3. Long Beach., 1997 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      The submission directive tells artists to "Send a SASE and a nude photo (cute art chicks only)."
    - Black Messiah, no. 1. Ellensburg., 1981 (Box 121, Folder 2)
      This is a Henry Miller tribute issue signed by Editor John Bennett.